{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": [
        {
          "Question": "Which streaming service is known for 'Stranger Things'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Netflix",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Hulu",
            "Amazon Prime Video",
            "Disney+"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Stranger Things' is a popular science fiction horror series exclusively available on Netflix since its release in 2016."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the alias of the lead character in 'The Mandalorian'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Mando",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Solo",
            "Skywalker",
            "Kenobi"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The lead character in 'The Mandalorian' is known as Din Djarin, but is commonly referred to as Mando."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Where is 'The Crown' set during its first season?",
          "TrueAnswer": "United Kingdom",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "France",
            "Russia",
            "Italy"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The first season of 'The Crown' primarily focuses on Queen Elizabeth II's early reign in the United Kingdom."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the title of the first episode of 'Black Mirror'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "The National Anthem",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Nosedive",
            "San Junipero",
            "Shut Up and Dance"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'The National Anthem' is the first episode of 'Black Mirror,' featuring a dystopian twist on contemporary society."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which Emmy-winning show centers around the fictional Roy family?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Succession",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "The Crown",
            "The Mandalorian",
            "Stranger Things"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Succession' is a darkly satirical drama following the power struggles of the wealthy Roy family and their media empire."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which actress plays the lead role in 'The Marvelous Mrs. Maisel'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Rachel Brosnahan",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Alex Borstein",
            "Marin Hinkle",
            "Amy Sherman-Palladino"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Rachel Brosnahan portrays Miriam 'Midge' Maisel, a housewife turned stand-up comedian in the acclaimed series set in the 1950s and 1960s."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'The Witcher,' who does Henry Cavill portray?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Geralt of Rivia",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Triss Merigold",
            "Yennefer of Vengerberg",
            "Ciri"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Henry Cavill stars as the monster hunter and protagonist Geralt of Rivia, based on the book series by Andrzej Sapkowski."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which actor plays the character 'Eleven' in 'Stranger Things'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Millie Bobby Brown",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Finn Wolfhard",
            "David Harbour",
            "Winona Ryder"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Millie Bobby Brown brings the enigmatic and powerful character 'Eleven' to life in the hit series 'Stranger Things.'"
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the AI in 'Westworld'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Dolores",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Arnold",
            "Maeve",
            "Bernard"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Dolores, portrayed by Evan Rachel Wood, is both a central character and an AI within the complex and thought-provoking narrative of 'Westworld.'"
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which streaming service premiered 'The Boys'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Amazon Prime Video",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "HBO Max",
            "Apple TV+",
            "Peacock"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'The Boys' is a dark and irreverent take on superhero culture, available exclusively on Amazon Prime Video."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Ozark,' what illegal activity does the Byrde family become involved in?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Money laundering",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Drug trafficking",
            "Arms dealing",
            "Human smuggling"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The Byrde family navigates the dangerous world of money laundering as they relocate to the Ozarks to escape a dire predicament."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which character becomes the 'Kingpin' in 'Daredevil'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Wilson Fisk",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Matt Murdock",
            "Foggy Nelson",
            "Karen Page"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Wilson Fisk, portrayed by Vincent D'Onofrio, transforms into the formidable criminal mastermind known as the 'Kingpin' in 'Daredevil.'"
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the title of the app used for dating in 'Black Mirror'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Coach",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Pair",
            "Match",
            "SoulMate"
          ],
          "Explanation": "In the episode 'Hang the DJ,' the dating app is named 'Coach,' which guides individuals through a series of relationships to find their ultimate match."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which character is the primary focus of the series 'Fleabag'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Fleabag",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Claire",
            "Martin",
            "Godmother"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The series revolves around the complex and darkly humorous experiences of the titular character, played by Phoebe Waller-Bridge."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'The Umbrella Academy,' who is Number Five?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Aidan Gallagher",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Ellen Page",
            "Tom Hopper",
            "David Castañeda"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Aidan Gallagher portrays Number Five, a member of the dysfunctional superhero family with the ability to travel through time."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which actor portrays 'Pablo Escobar' in 'Narcos'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Wagner Moura",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Pedro Pascal",
            "Diego Luna",
            "Javier Peña"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Wagner Moura delivers a captivating performance as the notorious Colombian drug lord Pablo Escobar in the gripping crime drama series 'Narcos.'"
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the main premise of 'The Haunting of Hill House'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Supernatural occurrences",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Alien invasion",
            "Zombie outbreak",
            "Natural disaster"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The series delves into the psychological effects of supernatural events and haunting experiences on the fractured Crain family."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which individual leads the team in 'The Expanse'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "James Holden",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Naomi Nagata",
            "Alex Kamal",
            "Amos Burton"
          ],
          "Explanation": "As a key protagonist, James Holden assumes leadership as the captain of the Rocinante in the expansive and immersive narrative of 'The Expanse.'"
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the main focus of 'Mindhunter'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Criminal psychology",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Space exploration",
            "Medical mysteries",
            "Time travel"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The series delves into the early days of criminal psychology and criminal profiling in the FBI, focusing on the Behavioral Science Unit."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Where does the dystopian society of 'The Handmaid's Tale' take place?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Gilead",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Panem",
            "Westeros",
            "Narnia"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The oppressive society depicted in 'The Handmaid's Tale' is situated in the totalitarian regime of Gilead, a theonomic military dictatorship."
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}